[Too Young To Love]
[Episode 13]
Yi Lan.
Anything else?
What's wrong?
Spit it out.
I like you.
Me?
Don't you have a girl you like?
Yes.
That girl has always been you.
I reject you.
The books are a bit messy.
The speaker is covered in dust.
It's been a few days since it was wiped.
It needs to be wiped.
Alright, alright.
Stop wiping. Stop wiping.
Move this cello to the repair room.
Be careful, it's a bit heavy.
Where are you going?
The repair room is this way.
Oh.
Tell me.
Tell you what?
You're definitely hiding something
from me.
Nothing.
Tell me now.
-It's hard to talk about.
-You have to! I give you 5 seconds!
Five.
Four.
-I'll say it then!
-Three.
Two.
One.
I'm going to say it.
-Say it!
-I love you!
Well...
Shan,
I think
I really have fallen in love with you.
The kind of love a girl has for a boy.
Do you know what Xiaoyi said love is?
Love is when your face gets really hot.
It turns red,
and your heart beats really fast.
That day, it was raining and you
held the umbrella for me, remember?
My face was very red,
and my heart was beating really fast.
And that's when I was sure.
Wait a minute.
I...
I've fallen in love with you.
Wait a minute.
Where did you go
during these days you disappeared?
I broke off my friendship
with Tong Xiaole.
The person you've fallen in love with
definitely isn't me.
The person I've fallen in love with
is you.
Do you know what love is?
Love is...
Love...
What's wrong?
Is there something on my face?
No.
See?
The person you love isn't me at all.
What's between us is just
a sibling-like bond.
Besides, in my heart...
there's always been someone
I can't let go of.
Siblings?
Then what is real love?
What is love?
Love is...
It's that kind of...
You want to be very close to him,
but you can't be that close. That...
That kind of feeling—
it hurts.
Do you understand?
You are...
Hello.
My name is Luo Ningzi.
I'm here for the interview.
Luo Ningzi.
Top of your major.
Luo Ningzi,
welcome to the Trio Orchestra.
Don't I need to play on site
for the interview?
Look. You're already top of your major.
No need for an interview.
Your cello skills must be very good.
By the way,
do you have time for a rehearsal
at 8 p.m. tomorrow?
Yes.
But I'd still like to ask
about the performance fee.
Don't worry.
It's much higher
than what you're expecting.
Here. See you tomorrow.
-Okay. I'll go back and prepare properly.
-Mm. Okay.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
You can come out now.
Yu.
Luo Ningzi is very outstanding.
Even without your recommendation,
she could still get in.
Top of her major at Hailan University.
I heard you...
like this watch very much.
No need. No need.
Just consider it me asking you
to take good care of Ning.
What?
Is she your girlfriend?
You even noticed that?
It's pretty obvious, okay?
By the way,
learning the cello is very expensive.
Right?
Is it okay for her
to work and study at the same time?
Ning's family...
ran into some trouble.
If she has any situation in the future,
just let me know privately.
But be sure to remember,
don't bring this up in front of her.
Don't worry.
That's good.
Sir.
Thank you for coming to see me
despite your busy schedule.
Mm. Not bad.
Let me introduce her to you.
This is our violist.
You played well.
Thank you.
Cai Yu,
your cellist
performed very well too.
Then... let me introduce her to you.
Okay.
You two chat.
In this field,
what expectations
do you have for yourself?
I want to keep improving.
Ning,
my mentor specially came
to see my performance.
The chief conductor
of the Dream Orchestra.
You must have heard of him.
Every music student probably knows him.
Besides,
I've seen him conduct a few times.
Then...
I'll introduce you to him.
Really?
Come.
What's wrong with you?
Something came up at your home again?
Listen,
if you get hammered later,
I won't take you home.
I'll ask Yi Lan to come get you.
Don't.
If you ask her to come,
I'll break off our friendship.
Seriously?
You confessed to her?
How did you know?
Did she tell you?
Even a fool can tell you like her.
So she rejected you?
I thought
we'd be together forever no matter what.
But...
now she's left me.
Forever?
Forever.
Really?
I...
Yeah.
Only you and I
can be together forever, okay?
Buddy.
Forever.
Chen Fan.
President Chen.
Mr. Chen.
For those words,
I must drink a toast to you.
Okay.
Today, however much you drink,
I'll drink the same.
You don't believe me?
Welcome to the broken hearts club.
How did you know?
Alright, alright.
Forget it.
Actually,
I...
We have both already very sincerely
expressed our true feelings, but...
when it comes to love,
it really is
something you can't force.
So I don't think you...
should blame Yi Lan...
too much.
Maybe,
perhaps,
probably,
you should...
just let it go.
After all,
you've known each other for so many years.
Continuing to be friends...
is pretty good too.
Are you blind?
Don't. Don't. Don't.
Screw you!
This is wonderful!
You hit me?
Guys, hit them!
Surround them!
What happened to your mouth?
It's nothing.
Shan.
That day,
I was too impulsive.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You...
So...
S-So,
the person... in your heart
has always been Professor Ye?
Then...
Then that day, why did you...
When I asked you...
Between you...
and Lan,
what's going on?
I confessed to her.
You confessed to her?
Didn't you tell me to confess to her?
I...
I didn't tell you to confess
in such a hurry.
You didn't say that that day, Shan.
Then let me
have a good talk with you today.
Do you know
what the most important thing in love is?
Distance makes the heart grow fonder.
You need to learn restraint.
You need to give her space to...
to grow and feel.
Restraint.
Understand?
[Do Not Disturb]
Distance makes the heart grow fonder.
You need to learn restraint.
[Student Practice Room 10]
I have a piece of bad news
and a piece of worse news.
Which one do you want to hear first?
The bad one.
The bad one?
Mm.
Xiaole...
confessed to me.
And?
What about the worse one?
I confessed to Shan.
What?
And the result?
The result is...
I rejected him.
And he...
rejected me.
Why did you confess to Shan?
I don't know either.
I thought I liked him.
What made you think like that?
But it's so weird.
After Shan rejected me,
I wasn't sad at all.
And I looked it up online.
They say the signs of loving someone
are... feeling jealous
and being possessive.
Mm.
And taking the initiative
to share your life with them.
Mm.
And taking the initiative to apologize.
I indeed have never acted
like that towards Shan.
Isn't that...
how you act towards Xiaole?
Mm.
Really?
What exactly is love?
I don't know either.
Look.
[Hailan University]
Say yes! Say yes!
Show the ring.
Yes.
Where's yours?
This video has gone viral
in the group chat.
They are such a perfect match.
-Mm.
Why did they break up?
I heard from classmates
it might be because
Professor Ye went abroad.
Look at this video.
Professor Ye was so lively and cheerful.
So different from how she is now.
Shan also told me
there's been someone he can't let go of.
He still can't forget her
after all these years?
Do you think
they've both stayed single
because they've been waiting
for each other?
Shan also told me
his understanding of love is
long-term companionship
and growing together.
Maybe...
they truly have been waiting
for each other.
Why think so much when in love?
That's way too complicated.
Mm.
My cello's endpin has arrived.
Oh.
Let me take a look for you.
Wait a second.
You're still using this cello
after all these years?
The endpin is worn out.
I have new ones.
Want to see them?
I've grown attached to it over the years.
Can you fix it?
Not sure.
It depends on whether the cello
is willing to be fixed.
You said before you lacked parts,
so I've been waiting.
What?
You went to fix the cello stealthily?
Who was being stealthy?
The parts arrived, so I just went there.
I saw you were in class,
so I didn't want to disturb you.
Stealthy?
Did you go specifically on that day?
It was a coincidence.
A coincidence?
This is the first record I gave you.
You've kept it all this time?
Of course I should keep it.
That record is pretty precious after all.
It's not like I have to throw it away
just because it was from you.
Well,
can you stop touching other people's stuff
without permission?
I'll leave the cello here for now.
I'll come get it another day.
Fix it well for me.
I'll let you know when it's fixed.
Xiaole!
What happened to your face?
My wisdom tooth is inflamed.
The light and shadow in my photos
haven't been great.
Can you take a look for me?
Sure.
[Characteristics of DSLR Cameras]
[Accurately Master
the Shooting Environment]
[Faster Focusing Speed]
Yi Lan,
are you close with Tong Xiaole
from the Department of Photography?
Are you his girlfriend?
I'm his childhood friend.
Why?
I see.
Then we all misunderstood.
I'm a sophomore.
Could you please help give this to him?
[I like you]
Xiaole.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I seriously thought
about what you said that day.
It was too sudden.
I think...
going from friends
to lovers
is a huge leap.
I...
I hope we can still be friends.
Is that okay?